[{"id": 563, "question": "Culture helps human societies survive in changing natural environment.For example, the end of the last Ice Age, beginning about 15,000 years ago, brought a big challenge to which humans had to adapt.Before this time, large parts of the northern hemisphere were covered in great sheets of ice that contained much of the earth' s water.In North America, large animals that wandered the vast tundra provided people with food and materials for clothing and simple shelters.When the earth became warm, large Ice Age animals disappeared, and many land areas were covered by rising sea levels from melting ice.But people survived, they developed new technologies and learned how to survive on new plant and animal species. Finally some people settled into permanent villages, durable houses and farms. Cultu...\n\nQ: To deal with the problems, human beings should   _  according to the passage.", "options": ["stop developing any longer", "reduce the overuse of natural resources", "stop the global warming and using natural resources", "save more animals in case they all die out"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3293, "question": "Bicycles are a great way to get around. They're fun to ride, especially down hills. And, as you speed along the road, you might also think of ways in which you could improve your bike-- make it safer, more efficient, or more comfortable. In fact, the two-wheeled machines make for some cool science projects. This year's Intel International Science and Engineering Fair (ISEF), held last May in Cleveland, featured(had)three bicycle projects from three countries. Like many of the other experiments presented at ISEF, the bike projects showed that some of the most interesting scientific research often begins by taking a closer look at things you care about. Renato Angulo Chu had even grander ambitions. The 12th-grader from Lima, Peru, wanted to _ some of his country's economic troubles. \"I see a...\n\nQ: It can be inferred that Renato's special bicycle is mainly designed for   _  .", "options": ["distant areas in the rainforest without electricity.", "the use of his own family to make life easier.", "the competition of ISEF to win money to support remote rainforests", "enough exercise by pedaling it"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2174, "question": "Summer school is something a kid will never forget.For some, it's a way to advance past their classmates.For most, summer school is' a requirement in order to graduate with their classmates I can remember being forced into taking a summer school course.It was not the school that forced me into this awkward situation it was my mother. I was a 16-year-old kid in a new school; My school did not offer summer courses so I had to take my course at an alternative school in the city.It was an experience I will never forget.I was not concerned with making friends.I was there to get credit for a course that I should have received credit for the previous semester.It was.my doing that landed me in the situation and it was important that I understood this. The fees were lowest but the experience was am...\n\nQ: Which of the following was NOT the benefit got by the author through attending summer school?", "options": ["It helped him get rid of bad habits.", "It helped him make new friends.", "It helped him understand what sacrifice and hard work were.", "It increased his independence."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1912, "question": "When we look at the sky and see a bright light moving quickly across it or coming towards the earth, we talk about seeing a \"shooting star\" or a \"falling star\". These moving lights are not, in fact, stars at all. They are small pieces of matter from outer space, which burn up as they enter the Earth's atmosphere. The correct name of them is meteoroids. Any pieces that make it to the Earth's surface without completely burning up are known as meteorites. A meteor is actually the name given to the light we see when a meteoroid is burning up. When a meteorite hits the Earth at speeds between 11 and 72 kilometers a second, it can do amazing damage. A very large meteorite could knock the earth out of its orbit. If this happened, all life on Earth would probably become extinct . The path we follo...\n\nQ: The Earth has   _  .", "options": ["three billion craters", "fewer craters than the moon", "more craters than the moon", "a thinner atmosphere than the moon"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 822, "question": "Long after the 1998 World Cup was won, disappointed fans were still cursing the disputed refereeing decisions that denied victory to their team. A researcher was appointed to study the performance of some top referees. The researcher organized an experimental tournament involving four youth teams. Each match lasted an hour, divided into three periods of 20 minutes during which different referees were in charge. Observers noted down the referees' errors, of which there were 61 over the tournament. Converted to a standard match of 90 minutes, each referee made almost 23 mistakes, a remarkably high number. The researcher then studied the videotapes to analyse the matches in detail. Surprisingly, he found that errors were more likely when the referees were close to the incident. When the offic...\n\nQ: What is one of the possible conclusions of the experiment?", "options": ["The ideal retirement age for an experienced football referee is 45.", "Age should not be the chief consideration in choosing a football referee.", "A football referee should be as young and energetic as possible.", "An experienced football referee can do well even when in poor physical condition."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3263, "question": "Dreams can be familiar and strange, fantastical or boring, but some dreams might be connected to the mental processes that help us learn. In a recent study, scientists found a connection between nap-time dreams and better memory in people who were learning a new skill. In the study,99 college students between the ages of 18 and 30 each spent an hour on a compute, trying to get through a virtual maze .The maze was different place each time they tired--making it even more difficult. They were also told to find a particular picture of a tree and remember where it was. For the first 90 minutes of a five-hour break, half of the participants stayed awake and an half were told to take a short nap .Participants who stayed awake were asked to describe their thoughts. Participants who took a nap wer...\n\nQ: What can we learn from the text?", "options": ["Participants who took a nap were required to express their thoughts.", "Some dreams may encourage people to invent something new.", "Participants who dreamed about films could finish the task more easily.", "Participants whose dreams had something to do with the maze could find the tree faster."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3264, "question": "Dreams can be familiar and strange, fantastical or boring, but some dreams might be connected to the mental processes that help us learn. In a recent study, scientists found a connection between nap-time dreams and better memory in people who were learning a new skill. In the study,99 college students between the ages of 18 and 30 each spent an hour on a compute, trying to get through a virtual maze .The maze was different place each time they tired--making it even more difficult. They were also told to find a particular picture of a tree and remember where it was. For the first 90 minutes of a five-hour break, half of the participants stayed awake and an half were told to take a short nap .Participants who stayed awake were asked to describe their thoughts. Participants who took a nap wer...\n\nQ: According to Stickgold,  _  .", "options": ["every person may dream about what they learned", "people's brain processes may still be connected with their learning in their dreams", "once people's eyes stop moving, they are sure to dream about something", "no matter how fantastical or boring, dreams are connected with people's life"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 730, "question": "The adder is the only poisonous snake native to Britain. Adders have the most highly developed poison injecting mechanism of all snakes, but they are not aggressive animals. Adders will only use their poison as a last means of defence, usually if caught or trodden on. No one has died from adder bites in Britain for over 20 years. By faar the most common smake in Britain is the adder. In Scotland, in fact, there are no other snakes at all. The adder is also the only British sanke with a poisonous bite. It can be found almost anywhere, but prefers sunny hillsides and rough open country, including high gournd. In Ireland there are no snakes at all. Most people regard snake bites as a fatal misfortune, but not all bites are serious, and very few are fatal . Sometimes attempts at emergency trea...\n\nQ: What should you do if you are with someone who is bitten by an adder?", "options": ["Catch the biting adder at onece.", "Don't worry about the bitten person.", "Don't try to treat the bite by yourself.", "Operate on the person as soon as possible."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1762, "question": "Up, Up, and Away! An adventurer who became the first person to fly across the English Channel on a cluster of balloons has launched a house into the sky just like in the hit movie Up-in reparation for a more ambitious journey and a new record Fearless Trappe , from North Carolina, stepped into the cartoon themed home before flying above the leon International Balloon Festivel in Mexico more than a week ago. The 38-year-old Trappe was using the event as a warm-up for his planned trans-Atlantic flight scheduled for next summer ,He aims to complete the 2,500-mile journey in a seven-foot lifeboat carried by 365 huge helium ballooms The brave man is learning to sail a lifeboat ,in case he meeds to ditch into the ocean during the danger-filled adventure He sill fly at between 18,000 feet and 25,...\n\nQ: The adventurer flew across the English Channel to  _", "options": ["test the balloons", "launch a house", "shoot a hit movie", "prepare for breaking a record"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1351, "question": "A jobless man applied for the position of \"office boy\" at Microsoft. The HR manager interviewed him and then watched him cleaning the floor as a test. \"You are employed,\" he said. \"Give me your e-mail address and I'll send you the application to fill in, as well as date when you may start. \" The man replied, \"But I don't have a computer, neither an e-mail. \" \"I'm sorry,\" said the HR manager. \"If you don't have an e-mail, that means you do not exist. And who doesn't exist cannot have the job. \" The man left with no hope at all. He didn't know what to do, with only ten dollars in his pocket. He then decided to go to the supermarket and buy 10kg tomatoes. He then sold the tomatoes from door to door. In less than two hours, he succeeded to double his capital. He repeated the operation three ti...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is TRUE?", "options": ["The man is one of the biggest food retailers in the world.", "The man didn't give up though he failed the interview.", "He started his career by selling tomatoes in the supermarket.", "Those who have e-mails can work at Microsoft."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 72, "question": "A new study has been carried to test the role of story telling in lowering blood pressure. Dr. Thomas Houston, a professor of the University of Massachusetts Medical School, led a group of scientists that investigated how pre-recorded videos of hypertension patients' talking about their medical histories helped another group of patients with high blood pressure to control their condition over several months. Houston was surprised by their studies that suggested that communication can be a powerful tool in medicine. They showed that those who had had similar experiences, when talking to someone with a similar background, could help change their behavior to become healthier. Hypertension is difficult to control, since it is dependent on diet, exercise and mental state. Medical treatments wit...\n\nQ: Houston was surprised to find that   _  .", "options": ["hypertension is really difficult to control", "communication has some medical effects", "medical treatments have no effect at all", "people don't follow the medical requirements"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1547, "question": "*200 dead as Brazilian plane crashes in Sao Paulo Up to 200 people were dead after a passenger plane with 176 people aboard slid off the runway on landing and hit a fuel storage tank at Sao Paulo's Congonhas airport on Tuesday. Brazilian airline TAM said that 170 passengers and 6 crew were aboard the Airbus A320 flying from Porto Alegre in southern Brazil to Sao Paulo when it lost control on landing and slid off the wet runway. Brazilian news agency Folha reported up to 200 people were dead, including some victims on the ground. * _ Two people were killed Saturday in two separate plane crashes in the United States, media reports said. In Dayton, Ohio, a plane crashed on a runway of the Dayton International Airport while performing during the Vectren Dayton Air Show. The pilot, Jim LeRoy, w...\n\nQ: The Brazilian plane crash caused extra deaths mainly because  _", "options": [".it skidded off the wet runway.", "the runway. was very short", "it hit a fuel storage tank", "its pilot was inexperienced"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3064, "question": "A single letter written by Albert Einstein was sold for more than $400, 000. But could an e-mail printout or an electronic file reach similar heights? That's the question facing those who deal in the literary artifacts of public figures, as they struggle to work out how to do business in the electronic world where information can be copied and spread out more easily than ever before. \"Booksellers, collectors and libraries are already trading in digital objects,\" Joan Winterkorn, a researcher told people. When Emory University Library bought author Slaman Rushdie's archives in 2006, it received a desktop computer, three laptops, a hard drive and a smart phone along with his paper flies. And the writer John Updike, who died last month, started using computers in the 1980s, Winterkorn pointed...\n\nQ: According to the text, the trade in digital archives   _  .", "options": ["has been well developed", "is still in its early stage", "is enjoying a period of prosperity", "is developing very rapidly"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3169, "question": "\"Our aim is to take our art to the world and make people understand what it is to move,\" said David Belle, the cofounder of parkour . Do you love running? It is a good exercise, yet many people find it boring. But what if making your morning jog a creative one?Like jumping from walls and over gaps and ground rolls? Just like the James Bond in the movie Casino Royale? Bond jumps down from a roof to a windowsill and then runs several blocks over _ on the way. It is just because of Bond's wonderful performances that the sport has become popular worldwide. Yes, that's parkour, an extreme street sport aimed at moving from one point to another as quickly as possible, getting over all the obstacles in the path using only the abilities of the human body. Parkour is considered an extreme sport. As ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE of parkour?", "options": ["It challenges human abilities.", "It is a good but boring sport.", "It needs special training.", "It is a team sport."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1577, "question": "\"Humans have a code of ethics ,\" says Marc Bekoff, an animal behavior expert at the University of Colorado. \" If I don't play in a certain way, you won't play with me. Some animals have the same code.\" Scientists recently discovered that animals that live in groups, such as elephants, foxes, and wolves, are especially likely to follow rules. If they don't, and each does its own thing, the group might break apart. Group members would be forced to live alone. Then they'd have a harder time hunting and raising their young. That's probably why a traveling wolf pack stopped and waited to let its slowly moving leader catch up. Similar social ties may have caused a captive elephant to save her friend from drowning. Selfish reasons certainly motivated the male fox, who wanted to keep playing. Some...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the passage?", "options": ["Humans have a code of ethics like some animals.", "Animals will follow certain rules in their group like humans.", "Scientists have made a great discovery about animals' behaviour.", "Animals go out of their way to do what's right."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2528, "question": "Scientists are using a kind of eye-tracking equipment to learn how babies look at the world. In the lab, children 5 months and older crawl and walk up, down and over adjustable wooden slopes , gaps and steps. It may seem like the set for a new reality television show, but there are no prizes, except perhaps for the researchers. They hope to understand what makes one child respond to another, how babies adjust their look to their hands and feet to handle objects, and how these very young children adapt to changes. The findings provided by these eye-trackers suggest that babies may be more capable of understanding and acting on what they see than had been thought. \"Quick looks at their mothers' faces may be all they need to get the information they want. They seem to be surprisingly efficien...\n\nQ: How do babies get the information they need?", "options": ["By using their own language.", "By looking at their mothers' eyes.", "By watching their mothers' facial expression.", "By listening to others."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1343, "question": "Pleasant Goat, lazy Goat, Beautiful Goat and Slow Goat, which one is your favorite? The second movie of the Chinese cartoon series of Pleasant Goat and Big Big Wolf again achieved noticeable box office takings in china, earning more than 40 million yuan merely three days after its debut . Pleasant Goat and Big Big Wolf is no doubt the most successful\"China made\"cartoon series recently. It is shown on TV almost every day and its core product can be seen almost in every child's goods store. It is the Chinese Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck. The cartoon series is not only welcomed by children, but is also often discussed among adult audiences. Pleasant Goat is appreciated for his courage and wisdom. While Big Big Wolf is considered a model husband though he is usually the bad guy in the story, a...\n\nQ: Pleasant Goat is liked because of his_.", "options": ["beauty and friendliness", "kindness and courage", "courage and wisdom", "beauty and wisdom"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2426, "question": "Learning a Second Language Some people learn a second language easily. Other people have trouble learning a new language. How can you help yourself learn a new language, such as English? There are several ways to make learning English a little easier and more interesting. The first step is to feel confident about learning English. If you believe that you can learn, you will learn. Be patient. You don't have to understand everything all at once. It is natural to make mistakes when you learn something new. We can learn from our mistakes. The second step is to practise your English. For example,write in a diary every day. You will get used to writing in English,and you will feel comfortable expressing your ideas in English. After several weeks, you will see that your writing is improving. Bes...\n\nQ: When you learn English, you do not need to   _  .", "options": ["be patient", "make mistakes", "express your ideas in English", "understand everything at once"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1988, "question": "Recently, South Korean star PSY's 'Gangnam style\" video has been popular on the Internet. It has become most people's favorite music. In fact, the song has set the Guinness World Record for the most popular video in the history of the Internet. More than two million people have said \"like\" since the song was on the Internet on July 15. PSY\"s special dance moves and funny horse riding style have attracted many people. Although many people do not understand the language, the video has become the talk of the Internet. The song has come to first place in the music charts in 31 countries, including the United States, the United Kingdom, and Canada. \"I just sang for my South Korean fans. I have never expected it to be popular in other countries,\" PSY told the reporters on a concert. The song was...\n\nQ: What makes PSY's \"Gangnam Style\" the famous music of millions of people?", "options": ["The song has set the Guinness World Record.", "The song has come to first place in the music chart.", "They like the dance moves and the horse riding style.", "They don't understand the words of the song."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2117, "question": "Although the weathermen's forecasts for a month ahead are only little better than guesswork, they are now making long-term forecasts into the next century with growing confidence. For the main trend (, ) in the world's climate in the coming years will, scientists say, be a predictable result of man's activities. At the start of the industrial revolution nearly two centuries ago, man set off a big experiment in planetary engineering. Unaware of what he was doing, he spared no thought for the consequences .Today the possible outcome is alarmingly clear, but the experiment is unstoppable. Within the lifetimes of many of us, the Earth may become warmer than it has been for a thousand years. By the middle of this century it may be warmer than it has been since before the last Ice Age. A warmer ...\n\nQ: Weathermen believe that our future climate will be the direct result of  _  .", "options": ["big scientific experiments", "clever long-term forecasts", "the industrial revolution", "planets changing course"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2332, "question": "A weather system known as a polar vortex brought dangerously cold weather to large parts of the United States this week. A polar vortex is a cold, thick low pressure system. The air turns counter-clockwise when on the move. The polar vortex started up in Canada. After crossing the border, it moved deep into the southeastern United States. The polar vortex brought the coldest temperatures in more than 20 years to many areas. Alice Jenkins lives in Washington D.C. \"I have a coat on. I have three sweaters. I have two blouses. But I don't feel like I have anything on.\" Another woman, named Amanda, lives nearby in Maryland. \"It's D.C. It's not supposed to be this cold.\" The extreme weather started with a low-pressure system near the North Pole. The Arctic air was pushed as far south as Alabama ...\n\nQ: Central U.S. was more severely affected by the cold because   _  .", "options": ["it was the place where the polar vortex was born", "it was too low here for the polar vortex to leave", "it was close to Washington,", "it was the cold air and high winds that stayed longer here"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 25, "question": "Very soon the Rabbit noticed Alice, as she went hunting about, and called out to her, \"What are you doing out here? Run home this moment, and fetch me a pair of gloves and a fan! Quick, now!\" Alice was so much frightened that she ran off at once in the direction it pointed to. She saw a little house, on the door of which was a plate with the name \"W. RABBIT\". She went in and hurried upstairs. By this time she had found her way into a tidy little room with a table in the window, and on it a fan and two or three pairs of tiny white kid gloves: she took up the fan and a pair of the gloves, and was just going to leave the room, when her eye fell upon a little bottle that stood near the looking-glass. There was no label this time with the words' DRINK ME,' but she opened it and put it to her li...\n\nQ: According to the passage, we can know that Alice   _  .", "options": ["felt comfortable when she grew no longer", "was afraid when the Rabbit called out to her", "knew what would happen to her if she continued to grow", "saw a label \"DRINK ME\" on the bottle and drank half of it"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2146, "question": "On the site of the 9/11 tragedy, Irish university professor Elizabeth Stinger Keefe found an image of hope-- a wedding photo of a happy couple and their friends lay among the rubble of the Twin Towers. As a gesture of goodwill, she decided to try and reunite the picture with either its owner or a . Every year, on the anniversary of the terrorist attacks, she would make an attempt, posting the picture on social media and asking others to share it. Finally, after a remarkable 13 years, her work paid off. Thanks to the power of social media, her appeal was more widely shared than ever before. A man named Fred Mahe called Ms Keefe after the image went viral -- to tell her that he was in fact in the picture and that all six people photographed were alive and well. He said that the image belonge...\n\nQ: Mahe's experience with 9/11 can be described as   _  .", "options": ["inspiring", "dangerous", "mysterious", "fortunate"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2463, "question": "For a long time now, I've been fascinated by common phrases and their origins- and just why we say what we say. I decided to consult the experts, sort through all the research and compile the answers. Here are a few of the standouts. Q: Why do we\"tie the knot \"when we get married? A: Knots have been a common metaphor in marriage ceremonies all over the world and through time. The expression means\"to unite in manage\". In the Hindu marriage ceremony, the groom ties a ribbon around the bride's neck. In ancient Rome, the bride wore a belt that was tied in a knot. The groom would then unfasten it on their first night together as husband and wife. Q: Why do we say\"Many happy returns\"? A: The phrase is short for\"Many happy returns of the day\", which is to say,\"May this day return many times\"or\"Ma...\n\nQ: The phrase\"It's not over till the fat lady sings\"was first used in   _  .", "options": ["sport", "opera", "movie", "music"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2000, "question": "One silly question I simply can't understand is \"How do you feel?\" Usually the question I asked of a man's action--a man on the go, walking along the street or busily working at his desk. So what do you expect him to say? He'll probably say, \"Fine, I'm all right, \" but you've put a bug in his ear--maybe now he's not sure. If you are a good friend, you may have seen something in his face, or his walk, that he overlooked that morning. It starts him worrying a little. First thing you know, he looks in a mirror to see if everything is all right, while you go merrily on your way asking someone else. \"How do you feel?\" Every question has its time and place. It's perfectly acceptable, for example, to ask \"How do you feel?\" if you're visiting a close friend in hospital. But if the fellow is walkin...\n\nQ: George Bernard's reply in the passages shows his  _  .", "options": ["cheerfulness", "cleverness", "kindness", "politeness"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2936, "question": "Crazy is our new normal. With two teenage boys and three little boys, our family is restless--to the baseball field, track field and piano lessons. Even though we've limited each boy's activities and try our best to defend our family time, it seems that we're in a constant state of flight. \"Embrace it. Roll with it,\" my husband, Lonny, says, \"It's going to be like this for a while.\" He is right. It's likely that life will continue to go forward before it slows down. But I remembered the still, quiet days that our family used to enjoy. I missed long walks through the park when we held the boys' little hands. I longed for lazy Saturday afternoons under the tree in our backyard. I wanted to slip back a few years, when busyness was the exception and not the rule. One night, after a particularl...\n\nQ: What does the author mainly talk about?", "options": ["Her anger at her busy life.", "Her family's struggle for a better life.", "Her new feelings about the present life.", "The pleasure of staying with her children."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1256, "question": "Yang Qunhui, 28, a graduate of Chengdu University of Information Technology, Sichuan Province, gave up her job with a monthly salary of 20,000 yuan ($3,014) at a famous company, but has started her own restroom-ad business with five other graduates, becoming a \"restroom queen.\" The company, opened in May, is now the only one of its kind in Chengdu. It has two goals: to find suitable restrooms to place ads and to find clients who are willing to put their ads in them. \"We are now trying to find restrooms to place the ads. A larger area means more ad sources,\" said Yang. Yang got the idea to run the company one year ago when she looked for toilet repairing information on the Internet but finally noticed companies in Beijing and Shanghai doing restroom ads. \"It's so interesting,\" she said. \"Ev...\n\nQ: Yang has started her business in order to   _  .", "options": ["do something she likes", "become a famous boss", "make money for her future", "make herself known to all"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2759, "question": "\"I would almost rather see you dead,\" Robert S. Cassatt, a leading banker of Philadelphia, shouted when his twenty-year-old eldest daughter announced that she wanted to become an artist. In the 19th century, playing at drawing or painting on dishes was all right for a young lady, but serious work in art was not. And when the young lady's family ranked among the best of Philadelphia's social families, such an idea could not even be considered. That was how Mary Cassatt, born in 1844, began her struggle as an artist. She did not tremble before her father's anger. Instead, she opposed him with courage and at last made him change his mind. Mary Cassatt gave up her social position and all thought of a husband and a family, which in those times was unthinkable for a young lady. In the end, after...\n\nQ: What do we know about Mary Cassatt's marriage?", "options": ["She never married because she did not want to be just a wife and mother.", "Her marriage failed because she never gave a thought to her husband and family.", "After marriage she decided to give up her husband rather than her career.", "She didn't marry because for a lady of her social position to marry below her was unthinkable."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3433, "question": "The small coastal town of Broome, in northwest Australia, is a remote village in the vast countryside. There are no traffic jams and hardly any roads. There is only the massive Australian wild land, where some houses are 500 miles apart and some driveways are 50 miles long. There seem to be only two main sources of entertainment out here: the sunset at the beach and Sun Pictures. Sun Pictures is a very different movie theater:The seats are park benches and deck chairs, but you're also welcome to sit on the grass. It is the world's oldest outdoor movie garden. Sun Pictures was built in 1916 on the other side of the globe from Hollywood. All the big films were shipped here and the lonely country was amazed. Broome resident Pearl Hamaguchi has never traveled far from home. But in the Sun Pict...\n\nQ: . It can be inferred that the tourists in Broome are most attracted by   _  .", "options": ["its peacefulness", "its beautiful sunset", "the Sun Pictures", "the gallery of movie stars"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2842, "question": "I want to let you know about an event that changed my life many years ago. We were living in College Station, Texas and my wife and I were on our way home from Houston, Texas one Sunday morning. We decided to stop at a local gas station to get something to eat since we had enough time. When we finished, we got back into our car and before I started it, we noticed a homeless man standing in front of the building. His clothes were worn and it looked as if he didn't have any money. It was cold and I was sure he wanted something to drink. However, it was not this that moved me. A dog was also walking up to the front of the building. Being a dog lover, I noticed that the dog was a mother and that she had just had some puppies . She was hungry and weak and I felt so bad for her. I knew if she di...\n\nQ: From the passage we can know that  _  .", "options": ["the author didn't like dogs", "the dog was not pretty enough to be loved", "the author wanted to help the dog but he was unable to", "the dog and her puppies were in danger of dying of hunger"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 611, "question": "Educating Girls Is a Real Lifesaver Clare Short knows it. Every developing economist knows it. The World Bank knows it. The education of girls is the surest way to reduce poverty. The reason is simple. All the evidence shows that taking girls out of the fields and homes, and putting them behind desks, raises economic productivity, lowers infant and maternal death rates, reduces birth rates, and improves environmental management. Why, then, are 90 million primary school-age girls around the world not in school? For the same reason that when Charles Dickens was writing David Copperfield 150 years ago girls were absent from the British education system: Men in power mostly prefer _ that way, or are not interested enough in changing the situation to commit energy and money to doing so. The cou...\n\nQ: Which is Not the reason why educating girls reduces poverty?", "options": ["It improves environmental management.", "It raises economic productivity.", "It creates more children.", "It lowers maternal death rates."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 569, "question": "Sheep, like turkeys and ostriches, are not considered the cleverest animals. British scientists said last Wednesday human may have underestimated the woolly creatures. They could be much smarter than we think. Researchers at the Babraham Institute in Cambridge, southern. England, have shown that animals have a good memory system and are extremely good at recognizing faces--which they think is a sure sign of intelligence. Behavioral scientist Keith Kendrick and his friends trained 20 sheep to recognize and distinguish 25 pairs of sheep faces and used electrodes to measure their brain activity, which showed they could remember 50 faces for up to two years. \"If they can do that with faces, the fact is that they have to have reasonable intelligence, otherwise, what is the point of having a sys...\n\nQ: From what Kendrick said in the interview we learn that   _  .", "options": ["scientists have learned a lot about sheep's intelligence", "scientists have learned little about sheep's intelligence", "scientists can't do anything more about sheep's memory", "scientists don't have to research animals' memory"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2973, "question": "My father, at the death of his father, was six years old, and he grew up without education. He moved from Kentucky to Indiana when I was seven. We reached our new home about the time the state came into the Union. It was a wild area, with many bears and other wild animals still in the woods. I grew up there. There were some so-called schools, but what was required of a teacher never went beyond \"reading, writing, and adding.\" If a stranger supposed to understand Latin happened to live for a time in the area, he was looked on as wizard . There was simply nothing to excite a desire for education. Of course, when I grew up, I did not know much. Still, somehow, I could read, write, and add, but that was all. The advance I have now made is on this store of education, which I have picked up unde...\n\nQ: How did the writer look at his early education?", "options": ["He believed he met the school requirements.", "He thought he was well-educated.", "He thought it was not satisfactory.", "He believed he was poorly educated."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1771, "question": "Who doesn't love sitting beside a cosy fire on a cold winter's night ? Who doesn't love to watch flames curling up a chimney? Fire is one of man's greatest friends, but also one of his greatest enemies. Many big fires are caused by carelessness. A lighted cigarette thrown out of a car or train window or a broken bottle lying on dry grass can start a fire. Sometimes, though, a fire can start on its own. Wet hay can begin burning by itself. This is how it happens: the hay starts to rot and begins to give off heat which is trapped inside it. Finally, it bursts into flames. That's why farmers cut and store their hay when it's dry. Fires have destroyed whole cities. In the 17th century, a small fire which began in a baker's shop burnt down nearly every building in London. Moscow was set on fire...\n\nQ: Many big fires are caused    _    .", "options": ["by cigarette", "by their own", "by dry grass", "by people's carelessness"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3277, "question": "Throughout life,change is the only thing that seems constant.Change has come to my 1ife many ways,in myself,and in my surroundings.At the same time,some things stay the same.This is when traditions are formed.I am often reminded of this by the photograph that sits by my bed. It all began with a kiss on my very first day of school.I remember dancing around the mirror,watching as my dark blue dress created a teacup around my waist.I admired the little ruffle of my shirt collar and how it matched perfectly with the trim at the bottom of my dress.I knew I would be the envy of all my classmates. But somehow,something was missing.I reached under my bed for the large box of bows ,in every color1 imaginable,that I was famous for.I picked out a white one that would match my shirt and carefully ran ...\n\nQ: How did the author feel when she dressed herself up?", "options": ["Disappointed", "Excited", "Nervous", "Embarrassed"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1633, "question": "Most people consider skydiving a product of the 20th century, but its history actually goes further back than that. The Chinese attempted to parachute in the 10th century, a thousand years before we did. The Chinese did what we would today call base diving; that is, they jumped off a place that would allow them to float from a height to the ground. The first person to attempt to parachute was a Frenchman named Jacques Garnerin. He jumped from his hot-air balloon at the end of the 18th century and did tricks on the way down and _ the crowds by landing safely on the ground. At the end of the 19th century, Kathie Paulus, a brave German woman, became famous for her skydiving skills. Once the airplane was invented, skydiving took on a whole new form. The airplane made it possible to dive from g...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for this text?", "options": ["The history of skydiving", "The popularity of skydiving", "What is skydiving?", "Why is skydiving an extreme sport?"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 607, "question": "No matter where he lives, 16-year-old Danny Lopez feels like an outsider: he is half-Mexican and half-white. At his private high school in wealthy northern San Diego, California, US, Lopez is too brown to fit in, whereas for the Mexican side of his family in National City, just a dozen miles from the border, he is too white to belong. Different from both sides, Lopez is silent in school. He focuses on his passion for baseball and working hard to improve the pitches that have kept him off the school team. Mexican Whiteboy, by Matt de la Pena, is about a teenager's search for identity. It was named as one of the Top Ten Best Books for Young Adults in 2009 by the US Young Adult Library Services Association. When Lopez's mother decides to go to live with her wealthy white boyfriend in San Fran...\n\nQ: Lopez and Uno have a lot in common except that   _  .", "options": ["they both have a divorced mom", "they both have mixed heritage", "they were both in the school baseball team", "both of them have big league dreams"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1661, "question": "About 10 years ago, I started a job as a trainer for a telemarketing agency.In one of my first classes, the head trainer told a very inspiring story. He began by drawing a stickman standing in the middle of a circle.To make it more interesting, he drew things like a house, a car, and a few friends inside the circle. He asked the question, \"Can anyone tell me what this is?\" In a long silence, one guy decided to throw out \"the world?\" The trainer said, \"That's close and this is your Comfort Zone.Inside your circle you have all the things that are important to you.\" \"Your home, your family, your friends, and your job.People feel that inside this circle they are safe from any danger or conflict.\" \"Can anyone tell me what happens when you step out of this circle?\" A strong silence came over the...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE?", "options": ["If we move beyond the Comfort Zone, our anxiety level will go up.", "When we step out of the Comfort Zone, we must feel excited.", "We don't need to leave our Comfort Zone if we really want to grow.", "We are all still in our Comfort Zone when making new friends."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 78, "question": "What's your idea of a good time? What about dancing in a rainy field with one hundred and fifty thousand other people while a famous rock band plays on a stage so far away that the performers look like ants? It may sound strange but that is what many hundreds of thousands of young people in the UK do every summer.Why? Because summer is the time for outdoor music festivals. Held on a farm, the Glastonbury Festival is the most well-known and popular festival in the UK.It began in 1970 and the first festival was attended by one thousand five hundred people each paying an admission price of PS1 -- the ticket included free milk from the farm. Since then the Glastonbury Festival has gone from strength to strength -- in 2004 one hundred and fifty thousand fans attended, paying PS112 each for a ti...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["The Glastonbury Festival is run on a profit-making basis.", "Tickets for the 2004 Glastonbury Festival were in great demand despite the high price.", "Both James Brown and Joss Stone were born in poor families.", "In the 1970 Glastonbury Festival, one could have lunch on the farm for free."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 382, "question": "To err is human. To blame the other guy is even more human. Common sense is not all that common. Why tell the truth when you can come up with a good excuse? These three popular misquotes are meant to be jokes, and yet they tell us a lot about human nature .To err, or to make mistakes, is indeed a part of being human, but it seems that most people don't want to accept the responsibility for the problem. Perhaps it is the natural thing to do .The original quote about human nature went like this: \" To err is human, to forgive, divine .\"This saying mirrors an ideal people should be forgiving of others' mistakes. Instead, we tend to do the opposite -find someone else to pass the blame on to. However, taking responsibility for something that went wrong is a making of great maturity. Common sense...\n\nQ: According to the author, what is a sign of a man's maturity?", "options": ["Doing things his own way.", "Bearing responsibility for his mistakes.", "Making as few mistakes as possible.", "Thinking seriously about his wrongdoing."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2137, "question": "When my son was just learning to talk, I carried him around the house in my arms and pointed out things to him. \"Look, David, a clock. \"He'd smile and point as I did and say \"clock\". David was quick at connecting the shape of things to their words. When my son was about four years old, I walked with him to the backyard. I knew that there was an ant colony under one of the slate stones in the walkway near the shed, so I said to David, \"Come on. I want to show you something. \" As I showed David the ants that were crawling around the slate stone, he crouched down on his legs and looked with great intensity at the ants. For days after that, David wanted to look under every rock in the garden, and we often found worms, ants and so on. I recognized that David loved to look at things closely and ...\n\nQ: Which of the following can best describe the author's viewpoint?", "options": ["Make children have their own hobbies.", "Teach children to be independent as soon as possible.", "Satisfy children's interest by possible means.", "Hobbies can determine one's future."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1431, "question": "1234 PENS is your No. 1 source for promotional pens, advertising pens, and logo pens. We have been in business since 1976, so you can be confident that you're dealing with a trusted name in the industry. Everyone loves a free pen, and by providing your customers with a pen featuring your company name, logo, or message, you can be sure that your company name will always be on their mind! Our custom imprinting service comes at no extra charge, so the price you see is the price you pay for the personalized pens. Do you need pens fast? In a rush for trade shows or a corporate events? Try our 48-hour promotional pens rush service free of charge. We present you with many styles and types of printed pen. Let us know which promotional pen you like and within 48 hours you will have the pens. Want t...\n\nQ: What do we know about 1234 PENS?", "options": ["It has a history of over 30 years.", "It has built up a large pen market.", "It has its name printed on each pen.", "It charges a low price for extra service."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2860, "question": "Homeschooling is the education of children at home, typically by parents but sometimes by tutors, rather than in public or private school. As a matter of fact, most childhood education occurred within the family or community. Homeschooling is a legal choice for parents in developed countries to provide their children with a learning environment at home. Parents see many reasons for homeschool, including better test results, improved instruction, to help the public system with fewer kids, poor public school environment, religious reasons, improved character development, the expense of private education, and objection to what is taught locally in public school. Homeschooling can also be a choice for families living in remote locations, living abroad, and to allow for more traveling. Also man...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE about homeschooling according to the text?", "options": ["Homeschooling is still illegal in developed countries.", "Athletes and actors can not be home-schooled.", "There is no curriculum for homeschooled children.", "Some parents have to homeschool their children when living abroad."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1627, "question": "Nick Vujicic was born with no arms or legs, but he doesn't let this stop him. The brave 26-year-old man plays football and golf, and swims, in spite of the fact that he has no arms or legs. Nick has a small foot on his left side, which helps him balance and makes him able to kick. He uses his one foot to type, write with a pen and pick things up. \"I call it my chicken drumstick ,\" joked Nick, who was born in Melbourne, Australia, but now lives in Los Angeles. \"I'd be lost without it. When I get in the water I float because 80 percent of my body is lungs and my drumstick acts as a propeller .\" \"He's very modest, but he gets marriage proposals from women all the time,\" said Nick's friend Steve Appel. \"He would love to get married and start a family, but he's waiting for the right girl to com...\n\nQ: What can we learn from what Steve Appel said?", "options": ["Nick Vujicic is serious about his marriage.", "Nick Vujicic is not popular with women.", "Nick Vujicic is afraid of starting a family.", "Nick Vujicic is not willing to get married."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2474, "question": "My mother used to ask me what the most important part of the body is. Through the years Iwould take a guess at what I thought was the correct answer. When I was younger, I thought sound was very important to us as humans, so I said: \"My ears, Mommy.\" She said: \"No. Many people are deaf. But you keep thinking about it and I will ask you again soon.\"Several years passed before she asked me again. Since making my first attempt, I had contemplated the correct answer. So this time I told her: \"Mommy, sight is very important to everybody, so it must be our eyes.\" She looked at me and told me: \"You are learning fast, but the answer is not correct because there are many people who are blind.\" Mother asked me a couple more times and always her answer was \"No. But you are getting smarter every year,...\n\nQ: The best title for this article might be   _  .", "options": ["The Most Import ant Body Part", "The Importance of family", "The Importance of the Shoulder", "A Life-long Question"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2701, "question": "Hubert Joseph Schlafly was an electrical engineer who helped change the way actors, politicians and other people speak on television. In 1950, he and two other men developed the teleprompter. One co-worker, Fred Barton, was an actor. He had an idea for a tool that would help television actors read their lines without having to memorize them. The other co-worker was Irving Kahn. He worked as vice-president of radio and television at 20thCentury Fox. The first teleprompter involved a person who held a long piece of paper printed with big letters. As the actor read the lines, another person would move the paper ahead on the device . The teleprompter was first used on a television program called \"The First Hundred Years.\" Later versions used television screens to show the words that were to be...\n\nQ: When using the teleprompter, people are able to   _  .", "options": ["memorize what they want to say very quickly", "practice their speech skills as if they were on TV", "face the TV while giving a speech", "see themselves on TV as they are making a speech"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3251, "question": "Most people buy a lot of gifts just before Christmas. But some people think we buy too much. They have started a special day called Buy Nothing Day. They don't want anyone to go shopping on that day. Buy Nothing Day is November 29. It's 25 days before Christmas. It's after Thanksgiving Day and often the first day of Christmas shopping. At this time, we see ads in Newspapers and on TV telling us to \"buy, buy, buy!\" The idea for Buy Nothing Day started in Vancouver, British Columbia. Now people all over the world celebrate Buy Nothing Day. In California, parents and children get together to read stories, sing songs, and paint pictures. The children talk about why they don't need a lot of toys. This year, in Manchester, England, people dressed up in costumes to tell people that we buy too muc...\n\nQ: How do people celebrate Buy Nothing Day?", "options": ["In California, parents and children get together to play games.", "In England, people celebrate by performing plays.", "In Mexico, high school students dress up.", "They buy nothing and persuade others not to buy things."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3053, "question": "One warm September night, Mira had come down to the beach to enjoy the night air. She closed her eyes and listened to the waves. Suddenly, she could hear another sound, so she opened her eyes and looked down at the sand. It was moving! All of a sudden she could see a tiny head coming out. Then a turtle appeared! One by one they struggled out of their underground nests. Mira looked in surprise at the baby turtles. Mira knew the turtles should head towards the waves and swim away, so she was puzzled when they began to pull themselves towards the dunes . Suddenly, she remembered something her grandmother had told her. \"Sea turtles bury their eggs on the beach every year in April and in September. Those baby turtles hatch and head back down to the sea. But some of them never make it. Sometimes...\n\nQ: How did Mira know the lights confused the turtles?", "options": ["She read it in a book.", "Her grandmother told her.", "She learned about the turtles at school.", "Her parents taught her about the turtles."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2065, "question": "With more and more wineries offering organic varieties to lower their eco-footprint , it's no surprise that they're looking at the environmental impacts of their packaging as well. The making of conventional glass bottles and the corks uses large quantities of natural resources and causes a lot of pollution. Beyond manufacturing, the transport of wine in glass bottles across the country and around the world also has its environmental effect. Trucking all the heavy glass bottles causes a much larger carbon footprint than the transportation of much lighter boxed wine. Almost half the weight of an ordinary case of wine comes from the bottles; about 95 percent of the weight of a case of boxed wine is the wine itself. \"A standard wine bottle holds 750 milliliters of wine and causes about 5.2 po...\n\nQ: What do we know about boxed wine from the passage?", "options": ["Corks are still needed to close it", "It's not suitable for long-distance transport", "It must be kept in the fridge during the transport", "The special packaging makes it stay fresh longer once it's opened"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3030, "question": "A news release is a tool of communication,through which information is passed to even the farthest end of the world.It keeps us well informed of the happenings of the world which would otherwise remain unknown. When writing a news release,keep in mind that the media receive hundreds of releases every day.Try to follow these guidelines:Keep it short and professional.Come up with a _ headline that will grasp someone's attention.Sometimes the title will take more time to come up with than writing the release.That's okay-the headline could be critical for getting an event covered! Cover the 5 W's in your first paragraph.Those are who you are; what you are doing;where,when you are doing;why you are doing it,which help us understand the details about the event.Besides,any opinions in the news re...\n\nQ: What is the most important for a news release according to the passage?", "options": ["Make sure the 5 W's in your first paragraph.", "Choose a proper spokesperson for the event.", "Make the news release newsworthy and accuracy.", "Ensure activists are prepared for the events in advance."], "answer": 2}]